Good morning,
everyone. You slept like hell.
I hardly slept at all.
It was too windy.
It's good that Riga has
a sleeping bag from
Kawas or else it's really
gg windy and cold.
The feeling is .... I've
been up all night again,
two days in a row.
It's a real mess. Yesterday,
we used the water next
to the campground.
It's clean, no bugs, and the only way
to tell is if you can see the bottom.
It's a really good source of water.
It doesn't need to be filtered,
so if you want to boil it,
it's a good source of water.
Just bring him to a boil.
No more filtration.
If you're going to drink it straight,
just strain it and drink
it straight, okay?
It's still windy in the morning.
It's windy everywhere.
We're ready to go.
We've been having a lot of headaches.
The whole face is swollen
(the steep grassy slope
east of Upper Cheuksak is
very sunny and steep).
If we go down this way,
we should set up camp around here.
Tomorrow we'll go up to the volcano,
another one to see the sky pool.
It looks clean.
Found a big backpack on the side
of the road (was there ever a.
.. A mountain disaster?)
Okay, we're officially
going to enter the
exploration route, general route 268.
We'll get to the Twin Peaks,
and then we'll do it all over again,
because of that one.
Well, it's over 3,000! So that's
why we're going to do this XD
So let's cut down to
the bottom now, dog!
Okay, we're going to cut down.
This is the way to Choksak East Peak.
Cut down early,
and this way? This is Twin Peaks.
And then the farther side is Iris.
And this one? The tallest
one is Kashe Datsun.
You can go to Grassy Hill,
then this is Sekigahama North.
（It's not very good.
You have to follow the tracks.
And then the roads are all
long and broken and steep,
and there's
--
There are paths,
but there are no paths,
so you have to drill them yourself.
Take a walk and you'll
see the fabric HERE!
There's a yellow strip on the front.
It's great. (The feeling of seeing
the strip on the expedition!)
Take it all! Taurine Green
Tea Caffeine RC Capsules
Electrolysis + O2 capsule to Pine
Needle down Twin Mountain,
hopefully with cloth.
Cloth Living
Water!!!
Wonderland (It's beautiful here!)
From the living water,
it's this kind of prairie.
The grassy slopes are
more of a ridge,
so it's a nice walk,
it's pretty cool.
Thinking of some of
the big south three,
Sighs Bay, it's gone this way.
The forest roads are great,
even if they're sunny,
but at least you don't have to get lost.
Compare directions
to the volcano.
There's a campground on the record,
Blackwater Pond, where you can set up camp,
Porcelain Bowl Campground.
If you don't have a bowl,
take this one. It's a big bowl from ancient times.
Savannah
Volcano
Send a message to the leader
that the original route
over the Twin Peaks should
have been taken.
It's gonna be a little
bit less fabric,
but for now, it's all there,
so we're just gonna go with it.
The fabric isn't too dense,
but it's basically all there,
honestly.
There are a lot of people
on this road,
I don't know where they're going.
I don't know if it's Iris or if
it's really Volcano Nangryo,
but I'm going around in circles.
I'm using Odlo now and
it's very light!
Tear
-resistant fabric + water repellant.
Well, it's kind of sun protection,
and it's supposed
to be a running jacket,
but I'm all about the weight.
Since it's less than 100 grams (it should be more than 100 grams),
I'll take it.
I'm using it as a sun jacket.
I've always used a patagonia
houdini jacket.
But that's the drawback. It'll break.
That's why we try not to wear them
when we're wearing shuttle arrows,
they're wider.
It's super cool inside the
forest! (Super breathable!)
I don't know where I'm going,
but there's a pool.
It's all about practicing
your sense of direction,
so you'll know what to do.
Where to go? To the
fork in the road.
It's a messy road,
but it's not dangerous.
Well now I'm going to
poop over here (?).
The environment is beautiful
and fragrant!
Cypress (full
of cypress!)
The Mouse of the Mountain,
down the hall.
You can spray this side,
too. You can spray everywhere. Up and down,
cut right, and then you're supposed to spray it in the
This is a great place to find a place
to cross the river and take a dip!
(Two trekking poles are recommended
for better stability)
Upper
cut.
Keep walking the stream. Hungry,
have a mango cocoa.
I'm really hungry! Pectin
is the best for this,
steep on!
I'm hungry. I'm hungry,
I'm hungry, I'm hungry,
I'm hungry, I'm hungry, I'm hungry.
It's basically just past this three
-way
fork that leads to Iron Mountain.
This way to the bottom,
there's not a lot of rags left,
so we'll just have to go to the tracks.
And then don't stray too far from it,
and find a good walk.
That should count for us now.
We just went down the edge,
so now we go up the edge.
Just go up on the pine needles.
I hope we can wait a while.
It should be okay.
Because we want to camp
somewhere there is a
Blackwater Pond and then go ahead
to a stone wall water source.
I hope we can
Add some more water. Now we start
from the most difficult part,
from the bottom of the stream.
I think this section of the
road is not difficult,
but I didn't expect it.
I took off my shoes when I was
crossing the stream because
Just cross the stream once and
the water is about knee deep.
Never cut upstream.
Always cut downstream.
Then you only cross the
river once so you can
If you take off your shoes,
it is recommended that you
do not hold or tie them.
Put it in your bag with
a large plastic bag.
Not too difficult,
perfect for chilling!
It's easy to walk. Of course,
it's not easy to do Zhuo Wan,
but I think this section of Twin Hills
Especially the front and back of Twin
Mountains are very beautiful.
Not bad, vacation, micro exploration,
this is not moderate nor advanced
It's a very basic exploration.
If you want to practice,
It's quite nice to
come here and there
are very few strips
of cloth like this
Let's wait for Cade to come up.
Looks like we've arrived.
It looks like Jiemaosi.
This should be the football
field camp. XD
There is water,
and black water is actually this (it is harder
to get than the football field camp)
We arrived at Gaoyi via
the relatively clean
Xiaochi (GPX reference for this time)
Camp 3, where we sleep, has two
small pools with dark water.
I think that side is better.
That side is better and flatter.
Arrived at 2:30 (I never
met him on this route)
Kai Hu! The new one
has this wind rope
Ancient things did not
finally know how
Build it flat (don't pull the two guy
ropes at the back yet! This is the key)
Four water bags,
a 500ml soft water bottle and a 1.
8L water bag
Another Befree 1L
should also be 1L
CNOC Shan
Manfu
Eat the ones with the shortest expiration date
first (a lot of them are about to expire haha)
Extra large tomatoes! Big bonus,
not filtered,
just cook them a little longer
There are some impurities,
it’s okay to cleanse the stomach
(?? Then there is the aluminum pot,
Boil bubble tea
quickly! ! ! !
This time I want to introduce the
Insta 360 GO 3S action camera
What is very special
about this camera
is that it has a magnetic detachable
It's a mother
-and-child machine,
so you can pull out the camera
and suck it back in like this.
Pull it out and suck it back in.
This one can be used
for 14 or 15 minutes.
The big one can be used
for more than two hours.
What is quite special is
that it does not need
The memory card can be
flipped up like this
to take a selfie of
your handsome face.
Now I can take a picture of me
I am OK like this (??
I can go out like this
It is very clear when
shooting outside.
Usually I will
The 2.7K 50P picture
is very sensitive
to light. It is quite special.
This actually works,
wow, the sports camera can
be extended like this
Pretty cool! The coolest thing is
this "magnetic function"
You can walk and shoot horizontally
and vertically
Shoot it straight and you have
a heart of steel! It can absorb
Go up and use this
lanyard to suck!
Just put the empty things on your
body and it's very convenient
You can free your hands
to find the way.
This is pretty cool.
The magnet can't be pulled off.
This time I also used Basis sandals.
If you don't need it yesterday,
you can go up the mountain today.
Let's take a nice
walk around the camp.
My teammate Cade
He has gone to bump into the
wandering and it is my turn.
This three days and
two nights "two
nights" is also based on
Yiwei can sleep well
but I couldn't
yesterday because of that
The wind and rain are clattering
(so annoying
It's useless
to eat anything!
There's no way I can
wake up after a nap,
but I hope I can have
a good sleep today.
Because the ground is very flat,
and the Japanese
I personally think it
is very effective.
You can eat it three to five days
before going up the mountain.
After eating,
you can fall asleep faster and
The quality of deep sleep helps
you use a GARMIN watch
I now use a GARMIN
watch to monitor
Your sleep quality
is also very useful
during the day because it can help
Your thinking becomes more flexible,
so I recommend it to everyone.
Because I have used a lot
of sleep health products,
this is
I think it's quite
effective. Of course,
you have to test it yourself.
It doesn't mean that what I think
is effective will work for you.
OK, I hope I can get a
good night's sleep
today because tomorrow
will be very hard.
Because we are going from 2500
meters above sea level
to 3200 meters above sea level,
so we need to
Climb to 700,
800, but the distance is not long. Anyway,
we just go directly
Shili Creek returned to the trailhead
and quickly followed our
The original teammates
went to meet up OK.
I hope they had a good time.
We are doing pretty well.
I didn't sleep well last night.
Staying up late for two days is
really a big collapse. Wait,
we have already eaten
in the afternoon.
One meal, then another
in the evening.
It's so chill.
You don't need to come to Twin
Hills for something like this.
You can go to Jiemaosi,
there are three to choose from,
but Jiemaosi
There is no water here.
It is highly recommended to go from
the location we just came from.
You can carry five or six liters of
water directly from the source.
There is no problem because
the distance is not
It's far away,
so you don't need to use the stagnant water here. Of course,
you have to use this side to see Tianchi.
That’s fine too because it looks
like Twin Hills is something
I sincerely and sincerely
recommend to everyone!
It's very chill. You don't
need to go to Nansan,
Caoshan Moji,
or the more difficult grasslands.
This is really quite simple,
including the six
-straight and three-day south
There are many such
terrains over there,
and this side is very easy to reach.
Recommended to you who are confused when
you walk to the mountain road:))
It will be better when the sun comes
out. We are going to this side,
Zhuoshe East Peak.
The pool is very large
so the water should be
flowing back from the
volcano to Mount Mu.
Now we should be preparing to
go to the volleyball camp.
There are several water holes
in the Pine Needle Campground,
and some are exposed to the sun.
The buttocks volcano,
right, take this ridgeline
Makiyama Triple Triangular Triangular
Triangular Kantakuman
Gan Zhuowan returns to Shili Creek